UNITE Communications Department Records 6000/037
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
UNITE Communications Department Records
1962-2003
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE)
6000/037
0.61 cubic feet
0.6 linear ft.
Records.
6179006
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 05, 2012
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 30, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6000/032: UNITE Communications Department Joann Mort Files 6000/037 AV: UNITE Communications Department Audio-Visual Materials 6000/037 P: UNITE Communications Department Photographs
Textile workers--Labor unions; Clothing workers--Labor unions; Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees.; Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union --Archives; Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees --Archives; Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees. Communications Department--Archives; UNITE HERE (Organization) --Archives
6179006
- UNITE Communications Dept., 1997 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- UNITE Communications Dept., 1985-1997 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- AFL-CIO, 1962-1972 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Hillman Logos, Ads, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Comm. Dept? UNITE, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Safety & Health + Safety, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Organization (Ind. 17-18), 1994 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- UNITE Newsletters, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Justice, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- United Hatters, AFL Affiliation, 1896 (Box 2)